<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[liamatchison]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[liamatchison]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 22:20:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Purveyor of Words]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Purveyor of Words</h1><p>Mr. Raye was not merely a scrounger, he was a purveyor of words. As far as he knew, he was the only one who made his living this way. He found this was the best way to survive in what was left of this suburb ever since the day the world fell apart. At first he had kept a calendar by making marks on the wall for each new day, but soon he missed a day, then two, then found himself hopelessly behind. He berated himself for his lack of discipline. A purveyor of words ought to be able to preserve the memory of time. This last thought intermittently assailed him, and he wallowed in it until he waved an arm backhandedly in front of his face and the guilt vanished. "After all," he reasoned, "I may be the first purveyor of words in this ugly, new world. It is enough that I remember some words and their meaning." </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/the-purveyor-of-words/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e623c582-6a8b-49e8-b351-336fceb4bbc6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 10:59:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ode to a dull pencil |]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ode to a dull pencil |</h1><p>In yesterday's post I discussed the adage that is the title of this blog. One of my late father's favorite adages was, "the dullest pencil is keener than the sharpest mind." he meant that I had better write down my ideas before I forget them.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/aaafc2a32308d7b3ce02163c29e461ed6f0dcc65.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://liamatchison.com/?p=456</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ca577a74-ad05-40cb-a6f8-1fc7fb8f8b29</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 05:58:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nipping home for a cup of coffee |]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Nipping home for a cup of coffee |</h1><p>Mediterranean cookery expert and coffee aficionada Claudia Roden once related the story of a Viennese man who loved java and conversation. Early in the day he found a seat and ordered his cup, which inevitably led to a convivial discussion for most of the morning.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/992938c7d1cfc517cfaab50c2e43427cae595512.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://liamatchison.com/?p=563</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">902ff8ce-7e82-46c6-a8fe-b8fab5273c4d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 05:35:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>