<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Flash Fictory]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Flash Fictory]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 05:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heidelberg]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Heidelberg</h1><p>Mr. Raye was not merely a scrounger, he was a purveyor of words. As far as he knew, he was the only one who made his living this way. He found this was the best way to survive in what was left of this suburb ever since the day the world fell apart. At first he had kept a calendar by making marks on the wall for each new day, but soon he missed a day, then two, then found himself hopelessly behind. He berated himself for his lack of discipline. A purveyor of words ought to be able to preserve the memory of time. This last thought intermittently assailed him, and he wallowed in it until he waved an arm backhandedly in front of his face and the guilt vanished. "After all," he reasoned, "I may be the first purveyor of words in this ugly, new world. It is enough that I remember some words and their meaning."</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f3a2087b7c79231d6fc5a85da6ca4f21026b0e6b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/the-purveyor-of-words/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e623c582-6a8b-49e8-b351-336fceb4bbc6</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 05:27:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Windmill at Coombebury Heath]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Windmill at Coombebury Heath</h1><p>The following letter was apparently lost in the mails until just recently. Many friends who read this little blog from time to time have asked about the story of the windmill that Maxwell began in his first letter. I am happy to report that I am now able to post Maxwell’s follow-up.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c5681515cc9d57c106b6f43715d4adf57b0307a3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/tilting-windmills-at-coombebury-heath/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">46eb5a5f-53cf-45f9-9f3e-4777785d270a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 05:14:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convivium Coffee]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Convivium Coffee</h1><p>Mediterranean cookery expert and coffee aficionada Claudia Roden once related the story of a Viennese man who loved java and conversation. Early in the day he found a seat and ordered his cup, which inevitably led to a convivial discussion for most of the morning. Suddenly he looked at the clock and asked his friends, “Would you mind saving my seat while I nip home for a cup of coffee.”</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c9d0056675ce030342e19069265fe734326fdca8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/nipping-home-for-a-cup-of-coffee-or/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">902ff8ce-7e82-46c6-a8fe-b8fab5273c4d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 03:54:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The beautiful English countryside]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The beautiful English countryside</h1><p>Maxwell Fleet</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/988f363339d75fc84245b90abdef34e2e91cde12.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/a-letter-from-coombebury-heath/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02971ae1-9ee9-4624-9d22-7c2603c0c8fd</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 20:34:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pencils]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Pencils</h1><p>In yesterday’s post I discussed the adage that is the title of this blog. One of my late father’s favorite adages was, “the dullest pencil is keener than the sharpest mind.” he meant that I had better write down my ideas before I forget them. I have just been thinking how much more powerful his aphorism would have been if the dullest pencil was also the best and the beautiful. In his youth America was still in search of a good five-cent cigar, but could wars have been averted with a superior penny pencil?There are the whole foods and tiny house movements. Perhaps there should be a Dull Pencil movement! Before you think I am suffering from lead poisoning from chewing too many Ticonderoga #2 barrels, allow me to elaborate.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5c99e16c774ad6678fc11605ed6cbfe6db6c58c5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/liamatchison/ode-to-a-dull-pencil/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">42ffcf84-caed-4497-bb19-8bf0a9fa0c5d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 20:20:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>